Lesson 60. Too early and too late. Punctuality is a necessary habit in all public affairs in civilized society.
第60课。为时已晚，为时已晚。守时是文明社会所有公共事务的必要习惯。
Without it, nothing could ever be brought to a conclusion. Everything would be in state of chaos.
没有它，永远无法得出结论。一切都会处于混乱状态。
rural: adv. 农村的, disregard: v.   不顾，无视
Only an aspartsly populated rural community is it possible to disregard it.
只有人口稠密的农村社区才有可能无视它。
punctuality: n.   准时
In ordinary living, there can be some tolerance of unpunctuality.
在普通生活中，可能会有一些不正常的宽容。
intellectual: n.   知识分子, coordinate: v.   协调
The intellectual, who is working on some obstruist problem, has everything coordinated and organized for the matter in hand.
正在处理一些obstruist问题的知识分子使一切都协调和组织了有关此事的协调和组织。
He is therefore forgiven if late for a dinner party.
因此，如果晚宴迟到，他会被原谅。
punctuality: n.   准时, reproach: v.   责备
But people are often reproached for unpunctuality when they're only fall this cutting things fine.
但是，当人们只跌倒时，人们通常会因不正常而受到责备。
It is hard for energetic, quick-minded people to waste time.
精力充沛，思想上的人很难浪费时间。
So they are often tempted to finish a job before setting out to keep an appointment.
因此，他们经常在出发之前要完成工作。
puncture: v.   刺破（轮胎）, diversion: n.   改道，绕道
If no accidents occur on the way, like punctured tires, diversions of traffic, sudden descent of fog, they will be on time.
如果途中没有发生任何事故，例如刺穿的轮胎，交通转移，雾突然下降，它们将准时。
They are often more industrious, useful citizens than those who are never late.
他们通常比从未迟到的公民更勤奋，有用的公民。
trial: n.   讨厌的事，人
The over-punctual can be as much a trial to others as the unpunctual.
对他人的审判可能与无关紧要的审判一样多。
The guest who arrives half an hour too soon is the greatest nuisance.
到达半小时的客人很快是最大的滋扰。
Some friends of my family had this irritating habit.
我家人的一些朋友有这种烦人的习惯。
The only thing to do was ask them to come half an hour later than the other guests.
唯一要做的就是要求他们比其他客人晚半小时。
Then they arrived just when we wanted them.
然后，当我们想要他们时，他们到达了。
fraction: n.   很小一点儿
If you are citing a train, it is always better to be comfortably early than even a fraction of a minted too late.
如果您援引火车的话，那总是比铸造的一小部分舒适地舒适地舒适。
Although being early may mean wasting a little time.
尽管早点可能意味着浪费一点时间。
This will be less than if you miss the train and have to wait an hour or more for the next one.
这将比您错过火车，不得不等待一个小时或更长时间才能到达下一个。
And you avoid the frustration of arriving at the very moment when the train is drawing out of the station and being unable to get on it.
而且，您避免了到达火车从车站抽出而无法上升的那一刻的挫败感。
An even harder situation is to be on the platform in good time for a train and still to see it go.
一个更困难的情况是在平台上享受火车的时间，并且仍然可以看到它。
Off without you. Such an experience befell a certain young girl the first time she was traveling alone.
没有你。当她第一次独自旅行时，这种经历困扰着一个年轻女孩。
She entered the station 20 minutes before the train was due.
火车到期前20分钟进入车站。
Since her parents had impressed upon her that it would be unforgivable to miss it and cause the.
由于她的父母给她留下了深刻的印象，即错过它并造成这种情况是不可原谅的。
Friends with whom she was going to stay to make two journeys to meet her.
她要和她在一起的朋友们进行两次旅程与她见面。
She gave her luggage to a porter and showed him her ticket.
她把行李交给了搬运工，并给他看了票。
To her horror he said that she was two hours too soon.
令她恐惧的是，他说她已经太早了两个小时。
She fell in here handbag for the piece of paper on which her father had written down all the details.
她掉进了这里手提包，写了父亲写下所有细节的纸。
Of the journey and gave it to the porter.
旅程，并把它交给了搬运工。
He agreed that a train did come into the station at the time on the paper and that it did stop.
他同意，当时的火车确实进入了纸上的车站，并且确实停止了。
But only to take on mail. Not passengers.
但只能接听邮件。不是乘客。
The girl asked to see a timetable.
女孩要求看到时间表。
Feeling sure that her father could not have made such a mistake.
感到她父亲不会犯这样的错误。
The porter went to fetch one and arrived back with the station master.
搬运工去取一个，然后带着车站主人回来。
flourish: n.    挥舞（打手劳）, microscopic: adj. 微小的
Who produced it with a flourish and pointed out a microscopic O.O. beside the time of the arrival of.
他以繁荣的形式产生了它，并指出了微观的O.O.在到达的时间之外。
The train at his station. This little O indicated that the train only stopped for mail.
他车站的火车。这个小o表示火车只停下来邮寄。
Just as that moment the train came into the station.
就像那一刻火车进入车站一样。
The girl tears streaming down her face.
那个女孩泪流满面。
Begged to be allowed to slip into the guards van.
恳求被允许滑入警卫面包车。
adamant: adj. 坚定的，不动摇的
But the station master was adamant.
但是车站的主人坚决。
Rules could not be broken and she had to watch that train disappear towards her destination while.
规则无法违反，她不得不看着那列火车在目的地时消失。
She was left behind.
她被抛在后面。